top10viral.com 2014-04-05

# Privacy - TOP VIRAL VIDEOS AND PHOTOS | TOP VIRAL VIDEOS AND PHOTOS

**Introduction**

Top10Viral.com  takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously.

This privacy policy, which we adapted from a policy originally provided by [Automattic](http://www.automattic.com/) ([WordPress.com](http://www.wordpress.com/)), describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our websites. Please read this notice very carefully.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Top10Viral.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Top10Viral.com  purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Top10Viral.com visitors use its website. From time to time, Top10Viral.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Top10Viral.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Top10Viral.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Top10Viral.com websites choose to interact with Top10Viral.com in ways that require Top10Viral.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Top10Viral.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for Top10Viral.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, Top10Viral.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Top10Viral.com. Top10Viral.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Top10Viral.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Top10Viral.com may monitor the most popular collections on Top10Viral.com. Top10Viral.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Top10Viral.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Top10Viral.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Top10Viral.com behalf or to provide services available at Top10Viral.com websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Top10Viral.com websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Top10Viral.com or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Top10Viral.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Top10Viral.com may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, Top10Viral.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Top10Viral.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Top10Viral.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Top10Viral.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Top10Viral.com website and have supplied your email address, Top10Viral.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Top10Viral.com and its products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Top10Viral.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

You should also be aware that if you submit information to “chat rooms,” “forums” or “message boards” such information becomes public information, meaning that you lose any privacy rights you might have with regards to that information. Such disclosures may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Top10Viral.com uses cookies to help Top10Viral.com identify and track visitors, their usage of Top10Viral.com websites, and their website access preferences. Top10Viral.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Top10Viral.com websites, with the drawback that certain features of Top10Viral.com websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any Top10Viral.com websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Top10Viral.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by Top10Viral.com. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Top10Viral.com does not own or control, or employees that Top10Viral.com does not manage. A Top10Viral.com website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and Top10Viral.com and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

**Security**

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Choice/Opt-out**

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices.

**Address Book Data**

Any external address book data (email contacts, etc.) that a user voluntarily gives Top10Viral.com access to will only be used for the described feature (looking up friends, etc.), and will not be stored or repurposed.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Top10Viral.com may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Top10Viral.com sole discretion. Top10Viral.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our sites in general, please [contact us](http://www.top10viral.com/contact/ "contact us")

Advertising keeps Google and many of the websites and services you use free of charge. We work hard to make sure that ads are safe, unobtrusive and as relevant as possible. For example, you won’t see pop-up ads on Google and we terminate the accounts of hundreds of thousands of publishers and advertisers that violate our policies each year – including ads containing malware, ads for counterfeit goods or those that attempt to misuse your personal information.

## How Google uses cookies in advertising

Cookies help to make advertising more effective – and that is what keeps thousands of websites free of charge. Without cookies, it’s harder for an advertiser to reach its audience, or to know how many ads were shown and how many clicks they received.

Many websites, such as news sites and blogs, partner with Google to show ads to their visitors. Working with our partners, we may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as to stop you seeing the same ad over and over again, to detect and stop click fraud, and to show ads that are likely to be more relevant (such as ads based on websites you have visited).

We store a record of the ads we serve in our logs. These [server logs](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/key-terms/#toc-terms-server-logs) typically include your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We store this data for a number of reasons, the most important of which are to improve our services and to maintain the security of our systems. We anonymize this log data by removing part of the IP address (after 9 months) and cookie information (after 18 months).

### Our advertising cookies

To help our partners manage their advertising and websites, we offer many products, including AdSense, AdWords, Google Analytics, and a range of DoubleClick-branded services. When you visit a page that uses one of these products, either on one of Google’s sites or one of our partners’, various cookies may be sent to your browser.

These may be set from a few different domains, including google.com, doubleclick.net, invitemedia.com, admeld.com, googlesyndication.com, or googleadservices.com. Some of our advertising products enable our partners to use other services in conjunction with ours (like an ad measurement and reporting service) and these services may send their own cookies to your browser. These cookies will be set from their domains.

See more detail about the [types of cookie used by Google](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/types/) and our partners, and [how we use them](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/cookies/).

### How you can control advertising cookies

You can use [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=en) to manage the Google ads you see.

You can also manage many companies’ cookies used for online advertising at the US-based [aboutads.info choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) page or the EU-based [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices).

Finally, you can [manage cookies in your web browser](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/managing/).

## Other technologies used in advertising

Google’s advertising systems may use other technologies, including Flash and HTML5, for functions like display of interactive ad formats. We may use the [IP address](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/key-terms/#toc-terms-ip), for example, to identify your general location. We may also select advertising based on information about your computer or device, such as your device model, browser type, or sensors in your device like the accelerometer.

### Anonymous identifiers on mobile devices

To serve ads in services where cookie technology may not be available (for example, in mobile applications), we may use [anonymous identifiers](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/key-terms/#toc-terms-identifier). These perform similar functions to cookies. To control the ads that we serve to apps on your mobile device, you can use our Ads Settings for apps. To change your preferences, or to opt out of interest-based ads, follow the instructions below for your mobile device.

#### Android

  1. Open the _Google Settings_ app on your device
  2. Select _Ads_

#### iOS

Some apps on iOS 6 devices use Apple’s Advertising Identifier; to learn more about limiting ad tracking using this identifier, visit the _Settings_ menu on your iOS 6 device. Legacy apps on your iOS 6 device, as well as apps on devices running older versions of iOS, may use a different device identifier. To opt out for these apps:

  1. Open the _Google Search_ app on your device
  2. Press the _Settings_ icon
  3. Go to _Ads Preferences_
